Hula, Erich; Papers ger044
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Individual Author Files, 6; 323 file folders
  - Pitkin, Hanna, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 40)
  - Plöchl, Willibald M., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 41)
  - Pollaczek, Gustav, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 42)
  - Pollis, Adamantia, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 43)
  - Pritchett, C. Hermann, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 44)
  - Rae, Douglas W., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 45)
  - Resnik, Solomon, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 46)
  - Rie, Robert, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 47)
  - Riedelford, Manfred. "Transcendental Politics? Legitimate Domination and the Concept of Civil Society in Kant", Undated; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 48)
  - Riley, Patrick, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 49)
  - Roche, John P., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 50)
  - Rogers, Lindsay, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 51)
  - Rolin, Henri E. A. M., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 52)
  - Rommen, Heinrich, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 53)
  - Rosinski, Herbert, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 54)
  - Rustow, Dankwart A., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 55)
  - Sack, Alexander N., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 56)
  - Salomon, Albert, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 57)
  - Sasse, Christoph, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 58)
  - Saveth, Edward N., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 59)
  - Schaefer, Morris. "The Nineteenth-Century Concept of Non-Civilized States in International Law", 1950; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 60)
  - Schapiro, J. Salwyn, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 61)
  - Schenk, Josef, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 62)
  - Schindler, Dietrich, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 63)
  - Schluchter, Wolfgang. "Beyond Scientific Rationality? On the Relationship between Religion and Science in the Modern World", 1982; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 64)
  - Schmitt, Carl, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 65)
  - Schubert, Glendon A. Jr., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 66)
  - Schürmann, Reiner. "Legislation - Transgression: Strategies and Counter-Strategies in the Transcendental Justification of Norms", 1984; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 67)
  - Schürmann, Reiner. "Philosophical Anti-Humanism: Marx, Nietzsche, Heidegger", Undated; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 68)
  - Schuller-Mintz, Ilse. "Erklaerende Bemerkungen zur Abschrift der Autobiographischen Notizen meines Vaters, Richard Schuller", Undated; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 1)
  - Schuller-Mintz, Ilse. "Richard Schuller. Autobiographische Aufzeichnungen, II. Teil, 1918-1953", Undated; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 2)
  - Schuller-Mintz, Ilse. "Richard Schuller. Autobiographische Aufzeichnungen, II. Teil. Fortsetzung", Undated; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 3)
  - Schutz, Alfred. "Symbol, Reality and Society", Undated; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 4)
  - Schutz, Alfred. "Equality and the Meaning Structure of the Social World", 1955; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 5)
  - Schwab, George, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 6)
  - Schwarzenberger, George, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 7)
  - Schwelb, Egon, 1954-1964; Reprints (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 8)
  - Schwelb, Egon, 1965-1972; Reprints (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 9)
  - Schwerin, Kurt, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 10)
  - Secher, Herbert P., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 11)
  - Shklar, Judith N., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 12)
  - Simon, Walter M., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 13)
  - Simons, Hans. Articles about, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 14)
  - Singer, J. David, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 15)
  - Smith, Jonathan Z. "A Report to the President on the Opportunities for Undergraduate Liberal Arts Programs at the New School for Social Research", 1984; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 16)
  - Smith, Maynard, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 17)
  - Sohn, Louis B., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 18)
  - Sorel, Georges. Articles about, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 19)
  - Speier, Hans, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 20)
  - Spiegelberg, Herbert, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 21)
  - Staudinger, Hans. Articles about, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 22)
  - Stein, Harold, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 23)
  - Stourzh, Gerald, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 24)
  - Strauss, Leo, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 25)
  - Strauss, Leo. Articles about, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 26)
  - Strisower, Leo, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 27)
  - Sulzbach, Walter, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 28)
  - Sumberg, Theodore A., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 29)
  - Swisher, Carl B., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 30)
  - Tammelo, Ilmar, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 31)
  - Taylor, Philip B. Jr., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 32)
  - Tenbruck, Friedrich H. "'Science as a Vocation' - Revisited", 1973; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 33)
  - Tenbruck, Friedrich H. "Die Soziologie vor der Geschichte", 1973; Typescript, mimeo (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 34)
  - Tenbruck, Friedrich H., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 35)
  - Thompson, Kenneth W. "The Charter of the United Nations: Realities and Review", 1955; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 36)
  - Thompson, Kenneth W., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 37)
  - Thompson, Wayne C. "The Politics of Kurt Riezler", 1973; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 38)
  - Thompson, Wayne C. Sections of book on Riezler, Undated; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 39)
  - Timasheff, N. S., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 40)
  - Tinder, Glenn, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 41)
  - Türcke, Kurt Egon Freiherr von, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 42)
  - Vagts, Alfred. "Die Chimäre des europäischen Gleichgewichts", 1942; Typescript (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 43)
  - Vagts, Alfred, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 44)
  - Vambery, Rustem, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 45)
  - van Langenhove, F., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 46)
  - van Well, Günther, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 47)
  - Verdross, Alfred, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 48)
  - Vile, M. J. C., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 49)
  - Vishniak, Mark, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 50)
  - Voegelin, Erich, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 51)
  - von Fritz, Kurt, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 52)
  - Walter, E. V., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 53)
  - Watson, Richard A., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 54)
  - Wechsberg, Joseph, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 55)
  - Wegner, Arthur, Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 56)
  - Weinberg, Albert K., Undated (Box 15 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 57)
  - Welch, William. "Kaplan's 'System and Process of International Politics'", 1958; Typescript (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 1)
  - Welch, William, Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 2)
  - Weyr, Franz, Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 3)
  - White, Howard B., Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 4)
  - Whyte, William Foote, Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 5)
  - Wolin, Sheldon S., Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 6)
  - Wolk, Stuart R., Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 7)
  - Woodward, Beverly. "Reason, Nonviolence, and Global Legal Change", 1973; Typescript (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 8)
  - Woolsey, Lester H., Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 9)
  - Wright, Quincy, Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 10)
  - Zernatto, Guido, Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 11)
  - Hans Kelsen publications, secondary materials, 6.291 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 12-44)
    - Hauptprobleme der Staatsrechtslehre, 1911 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 12)
    - Die Verfassungsgesetze der Republik Deutschösterreich. Erster Teil, 1919 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 13)
    - Die Verfassungsgesetze der Republik Deutschösterreich. Zweiter Teil, 1919 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 14)
    - Die Verfassungsgesetze der Republik Deutschösterreich. Dritter Teil, 1919 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 15)
    - Die Verfassungsgesetze der Republik Österreich. Vierter Teil, 1920 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 16)
    - Die Verfassungsgesetze der Republik Österreich. Fünfter Teil, 1922 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 17)
    - Das Problem der Souveränität und die Theorie des Völkerrechts. Beitrag zu einer reinen Rechtslehre, 1920 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 18)
    - Sander, Fritz.Rechtsdogmatik oder Theorie der Rechtserfahrung? Kritische Studie zur Rechtslehre Hans Kelsens, 1921 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 19)
    - Rechtswissenschaft und Recht. Erledigung eines Versuchs zur Überwindung der "Rechtsdogmatik", 1922 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 20)
    - Österreichisches Staatsrecht. Ein Grundriss entwicklungsgeschichtlich dargestellt, 1923 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 21)
    - Unrecht und Unrechtsfolge im Völkerrecht, 1932 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 22)
    - "Reichsgesetz und Landesgesetz nach österreichischer Verfassung", 1913 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 23)
    - "Rechtsstaat und Staatsrecht", 1913 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 24)
    - "Die staatsrechtliche Durchführung des Anschlusses Österreichs an das Deutsche Reich", 1927 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 25)
    - "Verfassungsreform in Österreich", 1929 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 26)
    - "Zollunion und Völkerrecht", 1931 April 24 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 27)
    - "Wer soll der Hüter der Verfassung sein?", 1931 August (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 28)
    - "Extrait. La Justice Platonicienne", 1932 November-1932 December (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 29)
    - "Das Urteil des Staatsgerichtshofs vom 25. Oktober 1932", 1932 November-1932 December (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 30)
    - "Die platonische Liebe", 1933 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 31)
    - "The Law as a Specific Social Technique", 1941 December (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 32)
    - "The Old and the New League. The Covenant and the Dumbarton Oaks Proposal", 1945 January (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 33)
    - "The Legal Status of Germany According to the Declaration of Berlin", 1945 July (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 34)
    - "Reine Rechtslehre und Egologische Theorie. Antwort auf: Calos Cossio, Egologische Theorie und Reine Rechtslehre, eine vorläufige Bilanz von Kelsens Besuch in Argentinien", 1953 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 35)
    - "Foundations of Democracy", 1955 October (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 36)
    - "Eine 'Realistische' und die Reine Rechtslehre. Bemerkungen zu Alf Ross: On Law and Justice", 1959 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 37)
    - "What is the Pure Theory of Law?", 1960 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 38)
    - "Plato and the Doctrine of Natural Law", 1960 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 39)
    - "Zur Frage des praktischen Syllogismus", 1968 May (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 40)
    - Kelsen, Hans. Articles about, Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 41)
    - Kelsen, Hans. Reviews of writings, Undated (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 42)
    - Hans Kelsen zum 85. Geburtstag. Special issue of Neues Forum, XIII, No. 154, 1966 October (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 43)
    - Kelsen, Hans. Obituaries, memorial addresses, 1973 (Box 16 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 44)
- Subject Files, 7; 174 file folders
  This series contains primarily newspaper clippings and other published materials on various topics, including American government and foreign policy, the Catholic Church, individual countries such as Austria, Germany, Great Britain, the Soviet Union and the United States, International Law, the New School for Social Research, and the United Nations.
  - Abortion, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Adams, John (and family), Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Adenauer, Konrad, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Africa, especially South Africa, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Aggression, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Algeria, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - America, literature on, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - American education, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - American foreign policy, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - American foreign policy, 1954 (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - American government, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - American literature, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - The American Society of International Law, Study Group on the Draft Articles on the Law of Treaties. Memoranda, reports, 1965 December 03-1966 October 08 (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Americans, famous, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Angola, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Anthropology, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Art, general, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Arms control, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Australia, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Austria and Austrians, Undated (Box 17 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20-21)
  - Baroque, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Belgium, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Blacks / Segregation, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - The Bricker Amendment, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - British Commonwealth, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - British literature, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Broadcasting - radio and television, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Calhoun, John C., Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Canada / Canadians, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Canon law, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Capitalism, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Catholic Church, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12-14)
  - China (Communist), Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - China (Taiwan), Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Church vs. State / Federal Aid to Education, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - C.I.A., Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Collective Security, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Common law, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Communism, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Computers, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Congo, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Crime / Penal reform, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Cuba, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Czechoslovakia, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Democracy, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Diplomacy, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Dumbarton Oaks, Undated (Box 18 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Economics, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Egypt, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Electoral process / voting, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Émigrés, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - European Defense Community, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - European Union / Common Market, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Fascism, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Federalism, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - France, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Frankfurt School / Institute for Social Research, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - French literature, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - German literature, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Germany, 1918-1933 (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Germany, East, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Germany, West, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Great Britain, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17-18)
  - Greece, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Hammarskjold, Dag, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Heuss, Theodor, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Higher education, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Hijacking, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - History, general, Undated (Box 19 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Human Rights, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Hungary, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Impeachment, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - India, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Indonesia, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Inter-American Treaty of Reciprocal Assistance, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - International Labor Organization, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Ireland, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Israel, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Italy, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Japan, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Journalism, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Judaism / Jewish topics, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Kant, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Kissinger, Henry, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Korea, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Labor, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Language / Semantics, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Latin America, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Law, American, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Law, Dutch, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Law, German, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Law, International, Undated (Box 20 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23-25)
  - League of Nations, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Liberalism, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - The Manilla Pact, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Marx, Karl, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Metternich, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Middle Ages (England), Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Middle East, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Mormons, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Multinationals, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Music, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - National Socialism, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Nationalism, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - NATO, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Naval power, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Neutrality, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - New math, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - New School for Social Research. Announcements, memos, 1939-1984 (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - New School for Social Research, Undated; Clippings (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - New York City, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - New Zealand, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Norway, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Nuremberg trials / war crimes, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Old Testament / New Testament, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Organization of American States, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Panama, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Papacy, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Peace - War, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Philippines, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Philosophy, Undated (Box 21 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Plato, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Poland, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Political science, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Politics, general, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Pornography, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Portugal, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Presidency / Presidential power, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Psychology / Psychoanalysis, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Religion, general / comparative, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Rhodesia, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Rome, Ancient, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Science, general, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Scotland, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - SEATO, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Slovenia, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Socialism, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Sociology, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - South America, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Soviet Union, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20-21)
  - Spain, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Spanish literature, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Südtirol, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Suez Canal Crisis, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Sweden, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Switzerland, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Terrorism, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Trusteeship Agreements, Undated (Box 22 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)